来一起狂欢吧!
Join the party!
救命!
Please!
你干嘛? 放手! 放手!
Whoa,whoa,what are you doing? Stop! Stop!
白人女性 身份不明
Caucasian female,no I.D.
怎么 城里搞嘉年华了?
What,the carnival in town?
是叛逆者的街头聚会
It's a  renegade street party.
自从市政府限制公众集会后
Ever since the city put restrictions on public gatherings,
他们就满城到处打游击
they've been popping up all over town.
那她穿得可太不应景了
I say she's a little overdressed for the occasion.
那个踩高跷跳芭蕾的说 她摇摇晃晃走到他跟前 然后就倒了
Ballerina on stilts over there said she just wandered over to him and dropped.
不知道她从哪儿冒出来的
No idea where she came from.
- 聚会是几点开始的?   - 午夜时分
- What time'd the party start?   - Midnight.
正在给他们录口供 目前为止 没人见到什么可疑事
We're taking statements from everyone.So far,no one saw anything suspicious.
脸部和颅部多处被撕裂
Multiple lacerations to the face and skull.
死因看来是钝器外伤致死
COD appears to be blunt force trauma.
看来她留了点线索给我们
Looks like she left us some clues.
是致命的线索
And they're deadly.
CSI:纽约篇 第五季 第4集 'Sex, Lies, And Silicone'
CSI:NY Season05 Episode04 'Sex, Lies, And Silicone'
嘿 Mac 这儿有些塑料碎片 我不确定是什么
Hey,Mac,got some kind of plastic shards here.I'm not sure what they are.
Danny 这儿有流媒体监控探头 在Hogan街和Lafayette街的街角
Danny,the city's got a streaming surveillance camera near here,corner of Hogan and Lafayette.
好 我去查查
All right,I'll go check that out.
死者手链上有些沾血的组织
There's some bloody tissue on our vic's bracelet.
手上及手腕上都没有防卫伤
No defensive wounds on her hands or wrists.
在街角泄洪沟里找到了死者钱包
Canvass found the vic's wallet in a storm drain around the corner.
里面有身份证 她叫Ann Steele
There's a photo ID inside. Here name is Ann Steele.
在几步远外的树丛里找到了 她的黑莓手机
Blackberry was found in the bushes a couple of feet away.
鸵鸟皮 价值不菲呢
Ostrich skin,pretty pricey.
公司专机登机卡
Corporate jet access card,
曼哈顿音乐学院的董事会成员 天蝎厅的VIP客户
board member of the Manhattan Conservatory, Scorpion Room VIP.
Wickfield公寓的门卡
Key card for Wickfield Condominiums.
像是个大人物
Sounds like a real mover and a shaker.
没有现金也没有信用卡
No cash or credit cards.
也许这就是动机
Could've just found our motive.
如果是抢劫 为什么不抢黑莓手机 钱包 值钱的玩意?
If it was a robbery,why toss the Blackberry? The wallet? Expensive items.
也许 他是个大白痴
Maybe he was just plain stupid?
我去把她的信用卡资料调出来 盯着它们的交易情况
I'll flag the credit cards. Keep 'em active.
找到她的名片了
Hey,found her business card.
"Ann Steele 专业顾问"
"Ann Steele,Professional Consultant."
她的记事簿里昨晚没活动
There's nothing listed in her calendar for last night.
怎么了? 看到什么了?
What? What is it?
Sinclair局长 她死前2小时 最后一通电话是打给他的
Chief Sinclair. The last call was to him two hours before she died.
嘿 你在这儿干嘛?
Hey,what are you doing in here?!
别跑!
Stop!
派保安过来!
Get me security!
每间办公室 每层楼都查了 目前还没发现侵入者
We searched every office and every floor. So far,no sign of an intruder.
在所有出口都派人站岗 以防他还在楼里
I want someone posted at every exit in case he's still in the building.
- 已经布置完毕   - 知道他怎么进来的?
- Done.   - Any idea how he got in?
保安说他亮了下徽章 说是来认尸的
Security guard said he flashed a badge and claimed he had to ID a body.
什么徽章?
What kind of badge?
他说没仔细看
Said he didn't get a good look at it.
已经把他撤职了
He's already been replaced.
Sid 看到他长相了吗?
Sid,you have a description?
白人 大概有6英尺高
Uh,Caucasian,around six feet tall,
穿黑牛仔裤 黑鞋子 他戴了兜帽
black jeans,black shoes; he was wearing a hoodie,
所以我看不清他的脸
so I didn't get a real clear look at a face.
他戴了双医用手套
And he had on a pair of surgical gloves.
所以没留下指纹
Means no fingerprints.
我想你不知道他在这里做什么
I don't suppose you have any idea what he was doing in here?
我进来时 他在尸体边转悠
He was hovering around the body when I came in.
找到部分鞋印
I got a partial shoe print.
我已把Steele的衣服和随身物品送楼上去了
I had already sent Steele's clothes and belongings upstairs,
所以除非他有恋尸癖 你和我想的一样
so unless he was into necrophilia,your guess is as good as mine.
好的
Okay.
从监控录像上找到闯入者影像了?
We get an image of the intruder on surveillance?
没 他似乎有意背对镜头
No,it looked like he deliberately turned his back toward the camera.
那也没引起当班警察的警惕?
That didn't raise suspicions with the security cop on duty?
他不是警察 Mac 他是局里逐步推行的 那种私人雇员
He's not a cop,Mac. He's one of those private hires they're phasing in.
那人只能算是戴徽章的普通人
The guy's basically just a warm body with a badge.
让训练有素的纽约警察下岗 换上未经培训的老百姓
Pulling experienced NYPD officers off posts and replacing them with undertrained civilians.
对想出这妙计 光会纸上谈兵的官僚们 真想狠狠抽一记耳光
I'd like to smack the pencil-pushing bureaucrat who came up with that brilliant idea.
说的就是我 Taylor警探
That would be me,Detective Taylor.
Sinclair局长
Chief Sinclair.
继续说 别停下
Go on,you were just saying?
是我 Flack
Yeah,it's Flack.
局长 我知道政府财政有点问题...
Look Chief,I know the city's having a few fiscal problems...
40亿的赤字不只是个问题 是危机
A $4 billion deficit is more than a problem. It's a crisis.
Mac 有人用了Ann Steele的信用卡
Hey,Mac. Got some activity on Ann Steele's credit card.
局长
Chief.
Ann Steele
Ann Steele.
市长知道后早上5点打电话给我
Mayor called me at 5:00 this morning when he got word.
他希望你优先处理这个案子
He wants this case moved to the top of the pile.
你就为这个来的? 教我怎么做自己的工作?
Is that why you dropped by? Tell me how to do my job?
听说今早有人闯了进来 我是为这个来的
I heard you had a break-in this morning.That's why I came by.
如果实验室的保安没外包给 最低价投标人的话
If lab security hadn't been farmed out to the lowest bidder,
就用不着你跑这一趟了
you might've saved yourself a trip.
雇1个纽约警察的钱 可以雇3个平民
For every NYPD salary we no longer pay,we can hire three new civilians.
你算算这笔账 警探
You do the math,Detective.
重点是"账本底线" 1个换3个
The phrase is "bottom line." Three people for one.
如果实验室保安有问题 我们经手的证物都会被人质疑
And if lab security is vulnerable,every piece of evidence we process can be called into question.
那笔帐该怎么算?
What's the bottom line on that?
我理解你的失望
I understand your frustration.
我也是奉命行事 像你一样
I get orders from the top,just like you.
我用不着喜欢那些决策 我只负责执行
I don't have to like them. I just have to make them happen.
"用最少的钱做最多的事"
"Do more with less."
好像你每年都跟我说一遍
Seems you tell me that every year.
每年你好像也都做到了
And yet every year,you seem to accomplish it.
接下来几周里
In the next few weeks,
你会收到进一步削减预算的建议
you'll be receiving recommendations for additional budget cuts.
你看 局长 我不...
Look,Chief,I don't...
新的现状就是如此 Taylor 面对现实吧
It's the new reality,Taylor.Get used to it.
那个闯入者 你知道些什么?
Now what can you tell me about this,uh,this intruder?
我更感兴趣你能告诉我些什么
I'm more interested in what you can tell me.
关于那个死者
About the victim.
这是Ann Steele的手机
This is Ann Steele's cell phone.
她死前2小时给过你电话 为什么?
She called you two hours before her death. What was that about?
她给我留言说她收到张非法停车罚单 想让我帮她处理一下
She left a message saying she had a parking ticket she needed taken care of.
你认识她? 你的邮箱地址也在上面
So you knew her?Your e-mail address is also in here.
我们在记者招待会上认识 还有几场慈善拍卖会
We shook hands at a press conference,a couple of charity auctions.
她凭到处网罗人脉营生
She earned her living by making connections.
你这样的男人对她那种女人来说 肯定是份巨大资源
A man like you would be a great resource to a woman like that.
相信我 Ann认识的比我权力大的 多了去了
Trust me.Ann had access to people a lot more powerful than me.
她名片上写她是个"顾问"
Her business card said she was a "consultant."
跟她所拥有的公司相比 那名头可真不起眼
That's a pretty generic title considering the company she kept.
知道她是哪种顾问吗?
Any idea what type of consultant she was?
传言她是帮人解决问题的 就是去摆平一些事
Rumor is she fixed problems.You know,made things go away.
我想我们说的不是逾期报税
I take it we're not talking overdue tax returns.
你还是盯着科学事实吧 Mac
Why don't you stick to the science on this,Mac.
政治的事我来管
I'll take care of the politics.
为什么我感觉你还有事没告诉我?
Why do I get the feeling you know more than you're telling me?
因为你是个警察
Because you're a cop.
你记住 我是你上司
Just remember,I'm your boss.
死者手链上的组织是种合成聚合物 不是人身上的
The tissue from the vic's bracelet is some kind of synthetic polymer. It isn't human.
她尼龙袜上找到的头发属于人类
Hmm,well,the hair I found on her nylons is.
是女性的 与死者的不相符
Results are female.Not a match to our vic.
也许是街头狂欢上谁掉的头发?
Maybe it's a random hair from the street party?
头发缠在她尼龙袜里 我想她跟谁有过身体接触
The hair was enmeshed in her nylon. I'm thinking close physical contact.
Stella 找到Ann Steele白金卡的 消费记录了
Stella,we got a hit on Ann Steele's platinum card.
有人刚用它买了一个扬声器
Someone just used it to buy an amplifier.
让Adam去分析聚合物 我们知道 它不是什么 让他来找出它是什么
Have Adam analyze that polymer.We know what it isn't,let's find out what it is.
好了 大家 演出结束 东西给我
Okay,folks,show's over. Give me these.
嘿 我正忙着呢 没看到?
Hey,I'm in the middle of my thing. Yeah?
我们也是 这是凶杀案调查
So are we.  It's called homicide investigation.
认识这个女的吗?
Do you know this woman?
- 从没见过   - 没见过?
- Never seen her.   - No?
- 你怎么搞到她的信用卡的?   - 我没有
- How'd you get her credit card?   - I didn't.
你在Conran电器店 用信用卡买了背上那个扩音器
You used it to buy that amp on your back at Conran Electronics.
你够蠢的 把名片落在柜台上
You were stupid enough to forget your business card on the counter.
嘿 嘿 你们干嘛?
Hey,hey,what are you doing?
照片上这个女人 她死了
The woman in that picture,she's dead.
好吧 我用了别人的卡 并不等于我就是杀人犯
Okay,just 'cause I used someone's card doesn't make me a murderer.
但你犯了重大盗窃罪
But it does make you guilty of grand larceny.
好吧 我在街上捡到那张卡
Okay,okay,I...I found the card in the street.
哪条街?
Which street?
市区里 我在参加个聚会
Downtown. I was at some party thing.
那个女的倒地死了 大家都被吓到了
Then that lady dropped dead,everyone was freaking out.
我就走了 回家路上捡到那张卡
I took off,found the card on my way home.
你为什么走? 要藏什么东西吗?
Why'd you leave? Did you have something to hide?
我穿溜冰鞋穿得脚起泡了
My roller skates were giving me a blister.
街头聚会之前你在哪里? 剪刀手先生 午夜以前?
Where were you before the street party,Mr. Scissorhands? Just before midnight.
我从公共剧院上了6号地铁
I was on the six train from Astor Place.
有谁能证明吗?
Anyone who can corroborate that?
Zach Rosenthal 我们一起搭车 去参加聚会的
Zach Rosenthal. We took the train to the party together.
踩高跷跳芭蕾舞的那个
Stilt-walking ballerina.
真没想到 在市监控录像上 看到个转呼啦圈很辣的妞
I never thought I'd say this,but I got some hot hula hoop action on the city surveillance tape.
- 凶案是狂欢开始前发生的?   - 没错
- I thought the murder happened before the party?   - Right.
- 那是Ann Steele   - 对
- There's Ann Steele.   - Yeah.
好吧 回到犯罪现场
Okay. Let's go back to the crime.
时间显示是11:55
Time code puts it at 11:55.
差不多是凶案发生时间
Right around the time of the murder.
死者遇害处的报纸自动贩卖机就在那
Okay,the newspaper dispenser where the vic was killed is over here
我就看到一辆停着的货车
All I see is a parked van.
是的 正好挡住了犯罪现场 就在货车后面
Yeah,and it's blocking the view of the crime scene,is right behind the van.
老大哥的能力也就这样了 (出自小说 时刻监控民众生活的政府)
So much for Big Brother.
等下 对街有户亮灯的窗边好像有东西
Hang on. Looks like there's a light in that building across the street,something in the window.
放大看看
I'm going in.
是个女人 面对犯罪现场
It's a woman,and she's facing the direction of the crime scene.
事实上 从那个角度看 她正盯着犯罪现场
In fact,based on that angle,she's staring right at it.
运气好的话 我们就找到目击证人了
Any luck,we just caught ourselves an eyewitness.
不记得她的名字了 不好意思 我 呃 昨晚有点喝多了
Can't remember her name. Sorry. I was,uh,pretty loaded last night.
听到外面有不寻常的声音吗- 奔跑 尖叫 大概午夜时分
Did you hear anything unusual outside-- any running,screaming,say around midnight?
什么也没有 怎么了?
No,nothing.What's this about?
你朋友呢? 她就在窗边 有没有提到看到什么了?
How about your friend there? She was in the window. Did she mention seeing anything?
- 我记得没有   - 你在哪遇上她的?
- Not that I remember.   - Where'd you meet her?
- 酒吧   - 酒吧? 哪家?
- Um,at a bar.   - Bar? Which bar?
Blue Tail 我想是这家
Blue Tail,I think.
那么 你们从哪弄到这张照片的? 我是说 你们找她做什么?
So,uh,where'd you get this photo? I mean,um,why are you looking for her?
我们认为她可能是罪案目击者
We think she might have witnessed a crime.
什么类型的罪案?
What kind of crime?
是我们在问问题 她几时离开的?
We're asking the questions. What time did she leave?
大约12点半 我不知道 我睡着了
Um,around 12:30. I don't know.I passed out.
好吧 帮我个忙 如果有她的消息 告诉她我们想找她谈谈
All right,do me a favor.You hear from her again,tell her we want to talk to her.
- 没问题   - 谢谢
- No problem.   - Thanks.
我去趟Blue Tail 看有没有人认出她
I'll pop by the Blue Tail,see if anyone recognizes her.
商务顾问Steele Slain身亡
Steele Slain Business Consultant Found Dead
- Sheldon   - Greg Pullman
- Sheldon.   - Greg Pullman.
你都在哪混呢 伙计? 藏在手机信号都没有的碉堡里?
Where have you been,man? Holed up in a bunker with no cell phone service?
我就职的那家律师事务所认为 一周工作少于80小时就是偷懒
Oh,my law firm thinks less than 80 hours a week is slouching.
你呢? 还在法医办公室工作?
How about you? You still at the Medical Examiner's Office?
不 我几年前就去了犯罪现场小组
Ah. No,I moved over to the Crime Scene Unit a few years ago.
你现在是权威人士了?
Oh,you're an authority figure now,huh?
你 呃... 在查Ann Steele的案子?
Hey,you,um... you on the Ann Steele case?
是啊 你认识她?
Yeah. You know about her?
是 她给我们的一个客户装了窃听器 勒索他到破产
Yeah,she wiretappeda client of ours,got him busted for extortion.
我们叫她女版鹈鹕
We call her the female Pelicano.
我想我们这些蹲实验室的 永远不会了解她有这么重要
I guess us lab rats never knew how important she was.
不是重要 而是有权势
Not important,but powerful.
你要是拿到她手上的资料 你这辈子就不愁吃喝了
You get your hands on her files,you'd be set for life.
还是你已经拿到手了?
Or maybe you already have?
我不能谈正在调查的案子
I can't talk about an active case.
- 是啊 没错   - 没错
- Yeah,right.   - Yeah.
好吧 事情结束后 我再跟你说说这些故事
Anyways,when this is over,I got some stories for you.
这女人的手伸得可长了 我老爹也是她的受害者
Woman had her fingers in a lot of pies. My old man's included.
Lowell?  他现在怎样?
Lowell? Wow. How's he doing?
他去年装了一个导管 但你了解他
Ah. He had a bypass last year,but you know him.
一周内就起床追逐护士了
He was up chasing nurses in a week.
- 代我向他问好   - 我会的
- Will you tell him I said hello?   - I will.
- 太好了   - 我会的
- Good.   - I will.
- 谢啦 见到你真高兴 Greg   - 我也是
- Thank you. It was good seeing you,Greg.   - Good to see you,too.
- 好的 伙计   - 保重
- Okay,man.   - Take care.
我明天有个庭审 但已经搞定了
Yeah,I had a,uh,trial scheduled tomorrow,but they settled.
提前庆祝也没关系
Wouldn't hurt to celebrate.
我们去酒吧喝一杯 找点乐子
Why don't we hit a bar,see what kind of trouble we can get into?
拜托 你最近都不照镜子的? 我们已经不是上大学那会了
Come on. You look in the mirror lately? We're not in college anymore.
拜托 Sheldon 我保证 绝不会惹你摆不平的麻烦
Oh,come on,Sheldon I promise we won't do anything you can't get us out of.
我们就像以前那样去喝一杯
Let's just go have a drink like old times.
好把
All right.
- 好的   - 好的
- All right.   - All right.
- Tanner's酒吧 8点   - 就Tanner's
- Tanner's at 8:00.   - Tanner's.
- 回头见   - 好的
- I'll see you there.   - Okay.
你就告诉你老板 我不在乎他多有钱 他的官多大
Well,you tell your boss I don't care how much money he makes or what his title is.
既然是犯罪证据 就要按规定处理 再见
I come across evidence of criminal activity,I'm going to act on it.Bye.
能打扰你一下吗?
Can I interrupt a sec?
这电话一早上响个没完
This phone has not stopped ringing all morning.
Ann Steele曾接触过的人 都打来问我们发现了什么
Anyone Ann Steele ever laid eyes on is calling to see what we got.
这案子让很多人紧张不已
This case is making a lot of people nervous.
你有什么发现?
What do you have?
没找到在窗边的目击者
No luck finding the witness in the window.
我和Blue Tail的酒保 还有几个雇员都谈了
I spoke to the bartender and several employees at the Blue Tail Bar.
都没有认出她或Trevor Jones
None of them recognized her or Trevor Jones.
她不会就这么消失得无影无踪
She didn't just vanish into thin air.
监控录像上有她 一定有人在哪看到过她
We have her on surveillance camera. Someone had to see her somewhere.
我们拿她的照片去附近地区筛查
We're canvassing the neighborhood with her photo.
- 有消息通知你   - 好
- I'll keep you posted.   - All right.
Ann Steele丝袜上发现的头发 在CODIS系统里找到了匹配记录
I got a CODIS hit on the hair I found in Ann Steele's nylons.
属于Jan Fowler 17岁
Belonged to a Jan Fowler.Seventeen.
有地址吗?
We have an address?
没有 她两年前就进了康涅狄格州的 失踪人口数据库
No. She's been in the Connecticut Missing Persons database for the past two years.
还有
And there's more.
康涅狄格警局对Jan Fowler的下落 没有任何线索 所以
Connecticut PD had no leads on Jan Fowler's whereabouts,so,
既然死者丝袜上发现的头发 是目前为止唯一的线索
since the hair I found on the vic's nylons is all we have,
我做了一个同位素分解
I did an isotopic breakdown on it.
她头发里氢和氧同位素的比例 显示她住在波士顿
Proportions of hydrogen and oxygen isotopes in her hair indicate  she'd been living in Boston.
所以我联系了波士顿警局 告诉他们她是桩谋杀案的头号嫌犯
Right,so I contacted Boston PD. I told them she was a lead suspect in a homicide.
他们传真来了这个
They faxed me this.
她死于吸毒过量?
She died of a drug overdose?
一年以前
Over a year ago.
一个死掉女人的头发怎会 出现在Ann Steele的丝袜上?
How'd a dead woman's hair get on Ann Steele's nylons?
嘿 看到Mac了吗?
Hey,have you seen Mac?
刚刚没有 怎么了? 有啥事?
Oh,not recently. Why? What's up?
解剖室的脚印有结果了
Oh,I got an I.D. on the footprint from the autopsy room.
入侵者穿的是10号耐克球鞋 黑色 没发现其他线索或DNA
Intruder wore a size ten Nike Air,black. No trace or DNA.
很好 我回头交上去
Great. I'll pass it on.
哦 你这... 呃 哦 有根睫毛
Oh,you have a... Uh. Oh.It was an eyelash.
那个你从Ann Steele手镯上 提取下来的合成聚合物
Okay,um,you know the synthetic  polymer you extracted from Ann Steele's bracelet?
我放大了400倍 说说你看到了什么
Well,I-I magnified it 400 times. Tell me what you see.
细胞结构之间有某种液体
I see some kind of liquid in between the cellular structure.
是胆固醇
It's cholesterol.
一种油脂 天然产的
An oil. Naturally occurring.
没错 所以我把悬浮于油脂组织中的 细胞分层
Right. So we have stratified cells suspended in an oily matrix.
是皮肤
It's skin.
但细胞没有细胞核
But the cells have no nuclei.
不是真的皮肤 而是人造皮肤
Well,it's not just any skin. It's synthetic skin.
实际上 是一种高级的 日本产的硅树脂皮肤
In fact,it's high grade,Japanese silicone skin.
用来保护键盘和电子设备 不被磨损和刮擦
They use it to protect keyboards and electronic devices from scuffs and scratches.
那怎么会在受害人的手镯上?
So what was it doing on our vic's bracelet?
我能... 我能找出来
I mean,I-I can...I can figure that out.
这儿有些塑料碎片 我不确定是什么
I got some kind of plastic shards here. I'm not sure what they are.
像是口红盖子
Looks like the top of a lipstick tube.
我也这么想
That's what I thought.
是U盘的盖子
It's a flash drive cover.
从制造商那里拿到了规格数据
Got the specs from the manufacturer.
64G存储空间
64 gigabytes of storage capacity.
比我的旧本本空间还大
That's bigger than my old laptop.
这个只是盖子 问题来了: U盘哪里去了?
And this is just the cover. Question is:Where's the actual drive?
在现场和受害人身上都没找到
Wasn't recovered at the scene or on the vic.
Ann Steele是个勒索者
Ann Steele was a fixer.
也许U盘里信息和她的谋杀案有关?
Maybe the information on that drive had something to do with her murder?
也可能和有人闯入法医办公室有关
It could also have something to do with the break-in at the ME's office.
外面有人还在找它
Someone out there is still looking for it.
我们得先找到它
Yeah,well,we need to find it first.
- 我去检查她的公寓   - 好的
- I'm go go check out her apartment.   - All right.
Ann Steele的公寓就在那个拐角
All right,Ann Steele's apartment should be right around this corner.
这算什么? 居然没管理员欢迎我们?
What is this? No super to greet us?
这样的公寓 他们可不叫管理员
This kind of money,they're not called supers,all right?
- 叫门房   - 哦 是吗?
- They're called concierges.   - Oh,yeah?
他们用门卡而不是钥匙
And they use key cards instead of keys.
听到了没?
Did you hear that?
纽约警局
NYPD.
想去哪?
Where you going?
- 别动   - 抓住他了?
- Don't move.   - You got him?
Anthony Martino 私家侦探
Anthony Martino,private investigator.
私家侦探 嗯?
Private investigator,huh?
Martino先生 你在做私家侦探前 曾干了6年的警察
Mr. Martino,I see you were on the force for six years before you became a P.I.
为什么离开? 毒品? 赌博?
Why'd you leave? Drugs? Gambling?
钱
Money.
你上次看到你的薪水支票是几时?
When was the last time you looked at your paycheck?
能找到那里还满厉害的嘛 这是什么 耐克球鞋?
Nice dogs you got there. What are those,Nike Airs?
我来猜猜 10号?
I'm gonna guess. Size ten?
这里是纽约 很多人穿这鞋的
This is NYC. Lot of guys wear these.
但并没很多人因偷窃 女死者的公寓而被抓
But a lot of guys weren't caught burglarizing a dead woman's apartment.
- 无主的住所 警探   - 没错
- Unoccupied dwelling,Detective.   - Right.
最多是三级入室行窃
Most I'll get is burglary three.
还能和检察官协议 降为非法闯入
And that'll get pled down to criminal trespassing.
两次了
Times two.
这双球鞋就能证明你 入侵过法医办公室
'Cause those sneakers are gonna tie you into the break-in at the M.E.'s office.
下次穿个鞋套
Should wear booties next time.
多谢 我会牢记于心的
Thanks. I'll make a note of that.
- 你在找什么?   - 你妹妹
- What were you looking for?   - Your sister.
真好笑 我没有妹妹
That's funny. I don't have a sister.
我换个方式问
Let me rephrase the question for you.
- 你为谁工作?   - 公民
- Who are you working for?   - People.
哪位公民?
Yo,people who?
确保我不会为此坐牢的人
People who are gonna make sure I don't do any time for this.
那个搜查Ann Steele公寓的家伙
The man who ransacked Ann Steele's apartment
和探查解剖室的是同一个人
is the same man we found nosing around our autopsy lab.
他叫Anthony Martino 是个私家侦探 以前是纽约警察
His name's Anthony Martino. He's a P.I. and former NYPD.
Martino 是个卑鄙小人
Yeah. Martino. He's a bottom feeder.
他告诉你他在找什么了?
He tell you what he was after?
有人付钱让他一个字也不说
Someone's payroll is keeping him quiet.
我们认为他是在找Ann Steele的U盘
We think he wanted Ann Steele's flash drive.
第一次没有找到
Since he couldn't find it the first time,
于是闯入她的公寓 希望在那交好运
he broke into her apartment hoping he'd have better luck there.
就是这样 他不是闯入 他用的是门卡
That's just it. He didn't break into her apartment. He used an access card.
目前为止 他绕过这两处的保安 还避开了监控摄像头
So far,he's bypassed security in two different buildings,and managed to evade surveillance.
你认为他有内应
And you're thinking there's an inside connect.
有高层在幕后操纵
Someone high up has to be pulling the strings.
去年 那个指控你性骚扰的案子 一夜之间就撤销了
Last year,that sexual harassment case that was filed against you went away overnight,
像从来没发生过一样
like it never happened.
你小心点 Taylor
You be careful,Taylor.
不要随便指控别人
Don't make accusations you can't back.
是Steele帮你摆平的? 所以你的名字存在她黑莓手机里?
Did Steele fix that for you? Is that why your name was in her Blackberry?
那是诬告
It was a false accusation.
我有孩子 幸福的婚姻
I have kids,a good marriage.
这一切都值得保护
Things worth protecting.
- 你没有回答我的问题   - 我不需要
- You didn't answer my question.   - I don't have to.
你看到她联系人列表上的名字
You saw the names on her contact list.
任何一个都有可能是幕后黑手
Any one of them could have been behind this.
如果这个U盘落入了坏人手中
If that flash drive falls in the wrong hands,
那引起的严重结果 可不是你能处理的 Mac
it'll cause more fallout than you can handle,Mac.
Adam 你想见我们?
Adam,you wanted to see us?
- Jan Fowler死了 对吧?   - 是啊
- Jan Fowler's dead,right?   - Right.
好 所以我就开始想
Right. So I started wondering
一个女死者的头发怎能跨过州界 跑到Ann Steele的尼龙袜上
how a dead woman's hair could cross state lines,and end up on Ann Steele's nylons.
所以我查了一下波士顿 处理她尸体的殡仪馆...
So I looked into the mortuary in Boston that processed her body...
等一下 我以为你还在钻研 Steele手镯上找到的硅树脂?
Wait a second. I thought you were working on the silicone we found on Steele's bracelet?
不 我是在弄 我刚才在弄 但我觉得所有证据都有联系
No. I-I am. I mean,I-I was,but I think it all just ties in together.
这里 看一下
Here,take a look.
这家殡仪馆因出售尸体器官 在接受特别调查
This mortuary in particular was under investigation for selling body parts.
- 在其它器官部分 他们还卖...   - 头发
- Among other things,they sold...   - Human hair.
这里是他们在纽约 有生意来往的2个地方
Now,there were a couple places in New York that they were doing business with.
我发现这和它们中的一个有关
And I found this link to one of them.
你是否想过找到一个完美女性会如何?
Have you ever wondered what it would be like to find the perfect woman?
欢迎来到精品人偶世界
Welcome to the world of high-end designer dolls.
嘿 姑娘 她可真辣啊
Hey,girl. she's hot.
我们的客户大多数是 想要女性陪伴的单身男性
Now,our clientele are mostly single men who want female companionship
但又不想碰到复杂的人际关系
without the complications of a human relationship.
一个标准人偶大约要6000美元
Now,a typical doll runs around $6,000.
我们是在找...
Well,we're looking for...
我们有10种不同的女性体型 和16种脸型
We've got ten different female body types and 16 faces.
这还不包括肤色 眼睛颜色 化妆
Not to mention skin tone,eye color,makeup.
我们对发色更感兴趣 金发
We're more interested in hair. Blonde hair.
我们什么颜色都有 颜色和发型随便挑
We've got every color.All shades and styles.
实际上 我们需要的是 你们购买金发人偶的客户名单
Actually,what we need is a list of your clients that bought dolls with blonde hair.
你的客户名单
Your customer list.
这有超过4000人啊
We've got over 4,000 of them.
都是这些皮肤的功劳 它们几乎能以假乱真
And it's because of the skin. It's almost like the real thing.
自从2007年来 我们开始使用 不可思议的新材料...
Since 2007,we've been using this incredible new material...
- 日本硅树脂   - 是的!
- Japanese silicone.   - Yes!
缩小一下你的客户名单怎么样?
How about we narrow down your customer list?
确切说 在纽约出售的 有着日本硅树脂皮肤的金发人偶
Exactly.Blonde dolls with Japanese silicone skin that were sold in New York City.
这里还有一个保密的问题
There's a confidentiality issue there.
大部分客户对他们的人偶 都相当注重保护隐秘
Most of our clients are quite secretive about their dolls.
那就是上帝创造搜查令的原因
That's why God created warrants.
- 我知道你们在想什么   - 想什么?
- I know what you're thinking.   - What?
我和它们有肉体关系
That I have carnal relations with them.
不 我没  那么想
No,I wasn't,uh,thinking that.
我没有 我从小就被教育当个绅士
Well,I-I don't.I was raised to be a gentleman.
所以 唔...这是Akiko Vanessa 还有Melody
So,um...Oh,um,this is Akiko, Vanessa and Melody.
她是家庭新成员
She's new to our family.
女士们
Ladies.
当我结束一天辛勤工作回家 她们总在这儿等我
When I come home from a hard day's work,they are always here for me.
她们给我平和舒适的感觉
They give me a sense of peace and comfort that
那种感觉是我在人类女性身上得不到的
I've never been quite able to achieve with a human female.
Gorem先生 我们来这儿 不是对你评头论足 真的
Mr. Gorem,we're not here to pass judgment,really.
我们在找一个金发人偶
We're looking for a blonde doll.
制造这些人偶的公司说 大约一年以前你买过1个
Company that makes these said that you bought one about a year ago.
Tiffany
Tiffany.
她-她的态度有些问题
She-she had a bit of an attitude problem,
所以我给她找了一个新家
so I-I found her a new home.
哪里?
Where?
在网上 有一个人偶粉丝的网站
On the Internet.There's a site for doll devotees.
我们交换新郎提示 初次约会故事 甚至交易人偶
We trade grooming tips,first date stories,we even trade the dolls.
你和谁做的交易?
Who'd you trade with?
我不记得他名字了
I don't recall his name,
但他带走了Tiffany 做为报答给了我可爱的Melody
but he took Tiffany and gave me lovely Melody in return.
她对我们更加合适 尽管她不怎么喜欢看电视
She's a much better fit for us. Although she doesn't really like to watch TV.
我们需要你的电脑
We're going to need your computer.
- 也许会有那笔交易的在线记录   - 好吧
- Maybe there's an online record of the transaction.   - Okay.
你知道吗? Gorem先生 我们还需要借用一下Melody
You know what?Mr. Gorem,we're also going to need to borrow Melody.
借-借用她?
Uh,b-b-borrow her?
她很可能携带前任主人的DNA
It's possible that she's carrying DNA from her previous owner.
如果你不记得他名字 我们就要带走她做些测试
And if you can't remember his name,we're gonna need to take her and do a few tests.
- 测试? 哪里?   - 在我们的实验室
- Tests? Where?   - At our lab.
至少我能不能和她一起去? 她很脆弱
Can I at least come with her?She is very fragile.
别担心 我们会很温柔的
Don't worry. We'll be gentle.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧 真是怪死了
Okay,how weird was that?
这玩意能替代有血有肉的女人 决不可能
There's no way that one of these can replace a real woman.
我不知道 Linds 她们长得还不赖
Oh,I don't know,Linds.They're not bad-looking.
想想男人能省下的晚饭钱
Think of all the money a guy could save on dinner.
一个人偶?!
A doll?!
如果你为其他女人甩了我 我能理解 但这堆塑料?!
I mean,I could understand if you dumped me for a real woman but a piece of plastic?!
她有什么我是没有的?
What does she have that I don't have,huh?
请原谅我的妻子 她脑子有点秀逗
Forgive my wife.She's not well.
我会帮你买的 Monroe 玩得高兴
I'm gonna get you for that,Monroe. Big-time.
1200万人口的城市 人们却需要人偶来作伴
A city of 12 million,and people need mannequins to keep them company.
他们怎么说来着 我们是独立的生物种类
I mean,what does that say about where we are as a species?
我不知道
I don't know.
我满脑子都在想这个可拆卸舌头
I'm still trying to wrap my head around this removable tongue.
我找到一个指纹
I've got a print.
怎么了 Adam?
Hey,what's up,Adam?
没什么 我...
Uh,n-nothing,I,um...
想知道你们是否需要些药签什么的
You know,wondering if you guys need some,uh... swabs or something.
不 这里一切尽在掌握 Adam 谢谢
No,I think we got it all under control here,Adam,thanks.
上帝啊 她太--我从没亲眼见过这个
God,she's so-- I mean,I've never seen one in real life before.
太栩栩如生了 我能摸摸她吗?
It's so realistic.Can I touch her?
Adam
Adam.
我走了
I'm going.
红发
Red hair.
我们就快好了 Melody
We're almost finished,Melody.
好了
Done.
指纹找到吻合的
Hey,I got a match on the print.
是Trevor Jones的
Belongs to a Trevor Jones.
他在总检察长办公室工作
He works for the Attorney General's office.
白天是这样 晚上则交易人偶
By day. Trades dolls by night.
讨论他的秘密生活
Talk about a secret life.
等一下 这不就是那个和Danny 还有Flack谈过话的人吗?
Wait a minute. Isn't that the guy that Danny and Flack talked to?
是啊
Right.
这个金发神秘目击者 在案发时正从他的窗口往外看呢
The blonde mystery witness was looking out of his window at the time of the murder.
哪种人目睹一起谋杀却不报案呢?
What kind of a person watches a murder and then doesn't come forward?
不能说话的人
One without a voice.
想我们吗?
Miss us?
没有搜查令你们不能闯进来
You can't just barge in here,not without a warrant.
看看我有什么
Oh,look what I got.
你的女朋友在哪儿呢 Trev?
Where's your girlfriend,Trev?
- 什么女朋友?   - 橡胶的那个
- What girlfriend?   - The rubber one.
Danny 是硅树脂
Danny,silicone.
对不起 硅树脂
Oh,sorry,right,silicone.
你们能不能告诉我这是怎么回事?
You guys mind telling me what this is about?
警探们
Detectives.
就是这回事
This is what it's about.
不是你们想的那样 好不好?
It's not what you think,all right?
我的同事跟我开玩笑给我的
Some of the guys at work got her for me as a joke.
好吧 从那之后她就在你床底积灰
Right. And she's been under your bed collecting dust ever since.
我们找到神秘的目击证人了
I think we just found our mystery witness.
拿稳了
Here we go.
就是她了
Oh,it's her all right.
你们不能带走她 她是我的财产
You can't take her; she's my property.
- 现在她是我们的了   - 不 不 等等 你们为什么带走她?
- Now she's ours. - No,no,no,wait.I mean,why-why are you taking her?
她和这件事有什么关系?
What does she have to do with this?
如果你女友的头发和硅树脂 和证据吻合
If the girlfriend's hair and silicone match our evidence,
- 那就证明死者来过你的公寓   - 所以呢?
- it puts the victim in your apartment.   - So?
你说你从没见过Ann Steele 那就意味着你在撒谎
So you told us you never met Ann Steele before. That would mean you lied.
我们去市区 再谈这事
We'll take a ride downtown and talk about this.
没错 看看 这就是男孩不该玩人偶的原因
Yeah,see,that's why boys shouldn't play with dolls.
我知道那个故事
I know that story.
为旧时光干杯
Here's to old times.
也为两点钟方向的黑发美女干杯
And to that brunette at 2:00.
- 老兄 你可没怎么变   - 我当然变了
- Man,you haven't changed a bit.   - Sure I have.
现在我可以请她喝一杯 还能买辆梅赛德斯送她
Now I could afford to buy her a drink. And a Mercedes.
你现在一定干得不错 他们让你调查Ann Steele的案子
And you got to be doing al right,they put you on this Ann Steele case.
你为什么一直提到她呢?
Why do you keep bringing her up?
对不起 我之前就该告诉你的
Yeah,I'm sorry.I should've told you this earlier.
我老爸 几个星期前 他把事情搞得一团糟
The old man,he screwed up pretty bad a few months back.
他处理财务问题时卷入了行贿丑闻
He tried to push some money around and got mixed up in this bribery scandal.
Ann Steele替他擦了屁股
Ann Steele mopped up the mess.
好吧 那有什么问题呢?
Okay,so what's the problem?
她把所有客户资料都放进U盘
She kept all her client's files on flash drives.
那些资料绝对会毁了我老爸的
Had more than enough to bury my old man.
你为什么要告诉我?
Why are you telling me?
我想我得把这些资料给删了
I guess I'm gonna have to put it out there.
如果你凑巧看到 任何和我老爸有关的证据
If you happen to come across any evidence that's tied to my dad,
他会感谢你的判断力 还有你的帮助
he'd appreciate your discretion. And your help.
所以你存心在办公室外偶遇我
So bumping into you outside my office,that wasn't an accident.
我不知道还能找谁帮忙
I didn't know where else to turn.
老实说 你只要删除有关他的信息就成
And honestly,all you're gonna have to do is just delete any information pertaining to him.
我不必做任何事
I don't have to do anything.
拜托 那和Steele的谋杀案 可没什么关系
Come on,it's not like it's connected to Steele's murder.
这不是问题的关键 这是篡改证据 你知道我不能那么做
It doesn't matter. It's tampering with evidence. And you know I can't do that.
法律上是不能 但是情感上...
Legally,no. But morally...
你还记得你在医学院的最后一年   --你得到的奖学金?
You remember your last year of medical school-- that scholarship you got?
记得 那又怎么了?
Yeah,what about it?
那是我老爸为了你捐给学校的
It was donated to the school on your behalf by my father.
Lowell为我付了学费?
Lowell paid my tuition?
他想要这么做
He wanted to do it.
他信任你 他觉得你会做出成绩的
He believed in you.He thought you were headed for great things.
你知道吗? 他没错
And you know what? He was right.
他很高兴能帮到你
He was happy to be there for you when you needed help,
现在 你也该回报他了
and now,it's your turn to do the same.
你这么说我可就不喜欢了 Greg
I don't like how this is sounding,Greg.
如果是真事 我很感激你父亲为我所做的
Now,if it's true,I appreciate what your father did for me.
但那是他的决定 不是我的
But that was his decision,not mine.
我不欠他什么
And I don't owe him anything.
嘿 Sheldon!
Hey,Sheldon!
记得她吗?
Remember her?
醉了不记得了 是吧
Nah,you were drunk. Right.
你杀她时也醉醺醺吗 还是那时清醒过来了?
Were you drunk when you killed her,or you sober up by then?
- 我不认识她   - 她叫Ann Steele
- I don't recognize her.   - Her name is Ann Steele.
她丝袜上发现的头发和你的小女友吻合
Hair we found on her nylon is a match to your little doll.
她手镯上的硅树脂 也和你的小女友吻合
Silicone on her bracelet,also a match to your doll.
我醉了 我不记得她的长相了
I was drunk.I didn't remember her face.
那你还记得什么 快说出来
Why don't you tell us what you do remember.
好吧 我们在酒吧遇上的 我把她带回家
All right,I met her at a bar,took her back to my apartment.
我们在客厅调情
We were in the living room fooling around.
她问我能不能去厨房拿点葡萄酒
She asked if I could go into the kitchen and get us some wine.
我回来以后就找不到她了
When I came back,I couldn't find her.
这是什么鬼东西?
Who the hell is that?
听我解释 就是个人偶
Uh,I-I can explain. It's um,see,it's just a doll.
- 天哪 你真变态   - 别 别 听我解释啊
- Oh,God,you're some kind of freak.   - No,no,no,I can explain.
- 我走了 变态!   - 等一下 等等!
- I'm out of here,pervert!   - Wait a minute,wait!
我发誓 那就是我最后一次见她
I swear,that was the last I saw of her.
你就让她那么走了?
So you just let her go?
随她知道你怪异的小秘密?
Taking your kinky,little secret with her?
事情就是这样的
That's my story.
我肯定陪审团会和我们一样觉得可笑
And I'm sure the jury will be just as entertained as we were.
你如果配合一点
Hey,if you play your cards right,
也许能让你以配偶身份 去看望你的小Tiffany呢
you might even be able to swing some conjugal visits with Tiffany.
你们也许能证明她去过我公寓
You might be able to prove this woman was in my apartment,
但你们没办法证明我杀了她
but you can't prove I killed her.
事实上 你们都没有足够证据逮捕我
In fact,you don't even have enough to arrest me.
只是现在还没有
Not yet.
- 晚安   - 你也是
- Have a good night.   - You got it.
快 快走
Come on,let's get out of here.
快跑!
Run!
Trevor Jones刚刚走了
Trevor Jones just walked.
你怎么了?
What the hell happened?
有人在我公寓外袭击了我
A couple guys jumped me outside my apartment.
有人? 什么人?
What do you mean guys? What guys?
我正在搞清楚
That's what I'm trying to find out.
是想抢劫吗? 是为什么?
Were they after your wallet?What?
我待会跟你说 Jones那边怎样了?
I'll fill you in later. What happened with Jones?
我们找不到血迹 没有确凿证据证明他谋杀
Uh,well,we got no blood,nothing to tie him to the actual murder.
Steele的U盘呢?
What about Steele's flash drive?
如果我们能在Trevor家找到 就能证明他和案子有关
We find that on Trevor,that's as good a connection as any.
他公寓里找不到
There was no sign of it in his apartment.
我所有地方都找了两遍
I checked everywhere. Twice.
如果能为了这东西杀人 肯定舍不得丢掉吧?
Well,if it was worth killing over,I doubt he would've just dumped it. Huh?
那问题就是:
All right,so the question is:
值钱的东西你通常藏哪儿?
Where do you hide something that valuable?
也许就在你觉得没人会多看一眼的地方
Maybe someplace you thought no one would ever look.
嘿 Mac
Hey,Mac,
我从Trevor Jones那里没收来的 人偶里找到了U盘
I found the flash drive in the doll we confiscated from Trevor Jones.
看你的样子 还被她狠狠揍了一顿?
Hmm. From the looks of you,she put up a hell of a fight.
是撞到健身房的墙上了
Yeah,The damn wall at the gym got in my way.
找到有用的线索了吗?
You get anything we can use?
Jones的指纹 还有Steele的血迹
Jones' prints. Traces of Steele's blood.
她肯定从他电脑里下载信息了
She definitely downloaded information off his computer.
他发现后就杀了她
And when he found out about it,he killed her for it.
里面还有其他小报编辑 做梦都想得到的丑闻内幕
I can think of a few tabloid editors who'd kill for it,too.
性丑闻 受贿 勒索
Sexual allegations,bribery,blackmail.
你只要提出来 Steele就能查得到
You name it,Steele was into it.
我就不用提醒你 里面的信息你得保密了吧?
I don't need to remind you that what you saw on this drive stays between me and you?
别担心 你知道我会支持你的
No worries. You know I got your back.
我也一样
And I got yours.
愿意跟我说说那堵撞到你的"墙"吗?
Why don't you tell me about that wall that hit you?
好吧
Okay.
一个所谓的朋友要我在U盘上做手脚 我拒绝了
A so-called friend wanted me to mess with that flash drive,and I refused.
他爸爸资助我上的医学院 他觉得这是我欠他的
His dad helped me out in medical school,and he thought I owed him.
你知道 其实我可以满足他的要求
You know,I could have given him what he wanted.
也不会影响这个案子 但我不会
It wouldn't have affected the case,but I didn't do it. I just couldn't.
Sheldon 这些你可以不告诉我的 不过谢谢你对我说了
Well,you didn't have to tell me that,Sheldon, but thanks.
你为了Ann Steele的U盘杀了她
You killed Ann Steele for her flash drive.
她说那是个唇膏
She said that was lipstick.
我们在里面找到了 与总检察长办公室有关的文件
We found secret files on it pertaining to the attorney general's office.
这是她从你电脑上偷的
Files she stole from your computer.
她不知道我在哪工作 她是偶然在酒吧搭识上我的
She didn't know who I worked for.She came onto me in a random bar.
因为她想接近你的电脑
Because she needed access to your home computer.
她很清楚你在哪儿工作
She knew exactly who you worked for.
她耍了你 Trevor
She played you,Trevor.
不 事情不是这样
No,it wasn't like that.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
噢 我唇膏掉了
Oh,I-I dropped my lipstick.
- 我帮你   - 不用了 我看到在哪儿了
- Let me help you.   - No,I see it,I see it.
我碰都没碰她
I didn't touch her.
你不想知道她在你卧室做了什么?
You didn't wonder what she'd been doing in your bedroom?
她走后 你也没注意到电脑是开着的?
And after she left,you didn't notice that your computer was on?
文件被下载了?
That files had been breeched?
你也没发狂一样跑到街上追她?
And you didn't chase her down in the street like an animal?
用力砸她的头 拿回自己的东西?
Bash her in the head to get back what she'd stolen?
没有
No.
- 把U盘给我   - 不
- Give me the flash drive.   - No.
嘿 给我 快给我
Hey,give it to me.Give it to me.
- 你什么都没做?   - 没做
- You didn't do any of that?   - No,I didn't.
那你怎么解释你的指纹和她的血迹 会在U盘上?
Well,then,how do you explain that your prints and the victim's blood are all over her flash drive?
也许是我捡起来的时候...
Maybe I picked it up.
没错 是我捡起来的
Yeah,I-I think I picked it up.
血迹在你指纹下面
The blood is under your prints.
只有一种可能性 就是你杀了她
The only way that could have happened is if you killed her.
你可能觉得我十恶不赦
You may think I'm a monster,
但我回家以后 看了Ann Steele U盘里的文件
but when I got home,and I read the files on Ann Steele's flash drive,
我意识到谁才是这个城市的恶人
I realized who the real monsters in this city are.
就是那些坐在董事会里的
They're the people sitting in the board rooms,
或者法官啊 被人英雄一般对待的人
running the courts,riding in the ticker tape parades.
你又能对他们做些什么?
What are you going to do about them?
他们没有杀人 Trevor
They didn't commit murder,Trevor.
你杀人了
You did.
Pullman!
你看起来糟透了 怎么回事?
Hey,you look terrible. What happened to you?
省省吧 Greg 我知道是你干的
Save it,Greg. I know it was you.
下次你雇人下手时
And the next time you hire a bunch of thugs,
可别再让人抓住证据了
you should make sure they don't have a criminal records.
我们已经抓到一个了 相信这时候他已把你供出来了
We've already picked one up,and he's flipping on you as we speak.
你打电话说要给我点东西
When you called me,you said you had something for me.
是给你父亲的
For your dad.
这可不是我期望的回报
Wasn't exactly the payback I was hoping for.
你找到U盘了吗?
You find the flash drive?
我看了关于你父亲的部分
And I read all about your father,
知道了他为了赢得招标所做的一切 威逼利诱 敲诈勒索
and everything he did to win construction bids-- extortion,bribes,threats--
想想我以前那么尊敬他
and to think I used to look up to him.
给我上思想道德课就不必了 Shel
Spare me the morality lecture,Shel.
你打算拿那些信息做什么?
What are you going  to do with the information?
我放到了你找不到的地方
I put it some place where you can't get your hands on it.
你开玩笑的 对吧?
You've got to be kidding. You're kidding me,right?
你想要什么? 要钱吗? 是这么回事吗?
What do you want? You want money? Is that it?
记得在坐牢前把支票给你老爸就行
Just make sure you give your dad that check before you get hauled off to jail.
我听说你破了案子
I heard you broke the case.
你不会大老远跑来祝贺我吧
My guess is,you didn't come all the way down here to congratulate me.
我想看看那个U盘
I'd like to take a look at the flash drive.
送去证物库了
It's on its way to the evidence warehouse.
你可真行动迅速啊
You don't waste any time.
由于这实验室保安不力 我觉得送到外面去安全很多
Well,since security at this lab is now in question,I thought it'd be safer off site.
对谁都好
For everyone concerned.
你想说什么就直说 Mac
If there's something on your mind,say it straight,Mac.
局长 你对我说谎了
You lied to me,Chief.
你说你那件性骚扰案是假的
You said that sexual harassment charge against you was false.
我也跟你说过不要对你没法证明的事情 妄下定论
I also told you not to make accusations you can't back.
那U盘上也有你的事情
Your file is on that flash drive.
你给了Ann Steele 25000元让她闭嘴
You paid Ann Steele $25,000 to keep that woman quiet.
我不想让这种事接受社会公众的评判
Because I didn't want it tried in the court of public opinion.
她的话会影响别人对我的判断
It would come down to her word against mine.
有罪无罪不重要 单单怀疑就够人受的
Innocence and guilt don't matter.Suspicion is enough.
那时我觉得有更重要的东西需要我保护   --我的婚姻
At the time,I thought I had something worth protecting-- my marriage.
那时候?
At the time?
U盘失踪的时候 我慌了
When that flash drive disappeared,I panicked.
我知道我给了Steele钱 就好像证明了我确实有罪
I knew the fact that I had paid Steele would make it look like I was guilty,
事实不是
but I wasn't.
你告诉你妻子了
You told your wife.
她要离开我了 Mac
She's leaving me,Mac.
现在想想 她已很长一段时间不开心了
When I think back on it,she hasn't been happy for a long time.
她只需要一个理由 让她离开的理由
She was just looking for an excuse.Something to allow her to go.
我亲自为她找到了理由
And then I handed it right to her.
我很遗憾 Brigham
I'm sorry,Brigham.